<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_3199813947" author="netupb" name="upb Restock Fleet Manager" description="*English (Google Translate)&#13;&#10;Allows automatic construction of exploding ships in a saved fleet (for commanders or all their subordinates).&#13;&#10;** For fleets whose Commander is a station, only the station itself cannot be construct.&#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;      To Enable / Disable, talk to the fleet commander's pilot or station manager.&#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;      When producing exploding ships, the loadout of the ships (including shields, weapons, engines and the slots they are installed in) will be preserved, the number of pilots/personnel and their ranks, assignment, group status and ship names.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;      Assignment changes resulting from explosions after activation are not taken into account (since fleet information is recorded). However, manual changes to the fleet structure, such as manually removing a ship from the fleet or adding an external ship to the fleet, automatically updates the fleet record.&#13;&#10;      If a registered fleet is connected to a new ship, the connected ship inherits the existing fleet registration.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;      Shipyard selection criteria for the ships to be produced;&#13;&#10;&#9;* You can create a blacklist for the wharf or shipyard you want in the settings menu for the production stations to be selected.&#13;&#10;&#9;  1- Can the relevant station produce the class to which the ship belongs?&#13;&#10;&#9;  2- Is the relevant station capable of producing ship chassis?&#13;&#10;&#9;  3- Are there enough relations to dock to the relevant faction station?&#13;&#10;&#9;  4- Does the relevant station have a shiptrader?&#13;&#10;&#9;  5- Are the military or capital ship licenses of the relevant station that will produce the ship open?&#13;&#10;&#9;  6- Can the blueprints of the equipment installed on the ship (shields, weapons, turrets, etc.) be provided by the relevant station?&#13;&#10;&#9;  7- Have the relevant station and the sector where the station is located been discovered by the player before?&#13;&#10;&#9;After these criteria&#13;&#10;&#9;  If the player has enough money (the ship cost is calculated based on the sellprice of the selected station),&#13;&#10;&#9;  Among the determined stations, the one closest to the RFM sector of the ship to be produced and&#13;&#10;&#9;  Priority is given to the station with an empty production slot on the production line.&#13;&#10;    &#13;&#10;      * Since the chassis and equipment blueprints of each faction can be learned in player shipyards, production controls will be easily passed. Thus, you can produce more easily.&#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;      If the actual command ship dies, the Promoted Commander temporarily executes the default order.&#13;&#10;      The real command ship takes over again when its construction is completed.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Note: For options screens can be accessed from the upb_Mods menu by talking to the NPC or player owned ships pilot or talk with Spec Officer Nurcan.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Missing points:&#13;&#10;&#9;1- In RFMs whose commander is a station, if the station is destroyed, the station is not rebuilt.&#13;&#10;&#9;   If this situation occurs, the relevant RFM will be disabled.&#13;&#10;&#9;2- When an rfm with an exploded ship connects to another rfm, existing ships will be connected. The exploded ship record will not be transferred.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;** RFM. Access Options:&#13;&#10;&#9;1- Talk to Player fleet commander or ship captain if not in the fleet&#9;&#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;a- In the '..more. (Mods)' option if ECM (Extended Conversations Mod) is installed &#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;b- else dialog #3 ( ! unless another mod has added this menu option. )&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;** UPB MODs. Access Options:&#13;&#10;&#9;There are 5 different methods to access UPB MODs.&#13;&#10;&#9;!!! If the option is not opened with the first 4 steps, you are probably using another mod that adds menu options. &#13;&#10;&#9;1- Talk to NPC ship captains. &#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;it will appear in the bottom left (#3) position.&#13;&#10;&#9;2- Talk to any player ship captain or player station managers. &#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;Under the more option, if no other mod has added it to the menu options, it will appear in the left (#2) position.&#13;&#10;&#9;3- Talk to Player fleet commander or ship captain if not in the fleet&#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;a- if there is a &quot;..more. (Mods)&quot; option, that is, if ECM (Extended Conversations Mod v0.20 on Nexus) is installed, it is in this menu.&#13;&#10;&#9;4- Talk to any subordinate ship in the player's fleet&#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;a- if there is a &quot;..more. (Mods)&quot; option, that is, if ECM (Extended Conversations Mod v0.20 on Nexus) is installed, it is in this menu.&#13;&#10;&#9;&#9;b- Otherwise it will appear in an empty slot (#3) in the menu. ( ! unless another mod(s) has added this menu option. )&#13;&#10;&#9;5- In this case, use the 'Upb Equipment Modification And Reqruit Service' Mod. &#13;&#10;&#9;   This new mode assigns a Spec officer you can talk to when you land at the shipyard or wharf (player or npc) stations. &#13;&#10;&#9;   To access UPB MODs, talk to Spec. Officer Nurcan ARIKAN HOS.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Türkçe:&#13;&#10;Kayıtlı bir filodaki patlayan gemilerin (komutanlar ya da tüm astları için) otomatik olarak inşa edilmesini sağlar.&#13;&#10;** Commanderi istasyon olan filolar için sadece istasyonun kendisi üretilemiyor . &#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;     Enable / Disable için filo komutanının pilotu ya da istasyon manageri ile konuş.&#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;     Patlayan gemiler üretilirken gemilerin loadout (kalkan, silah, motor ve takılı olduğu slotlara kadar  aynı gemi üretilecek), pilot/personel sayısı ve rütbeleri, assignment, group durumları ve gemi adları korunacak. &#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;     Enable olduktan sonraki patlamalardan kaynaklanan assigment değişimler dikkate alınmaz.(Filo bilgisi kayıt altında olduğu için) . Ama, filodaki bir geminin manuel çıkartılması ya da filoya dışardan bir gemi eklenmesi gibi filo yapısındaki manuel değişiklikler filo kaydını otomatik günceller.&#13;&#10;      Kayıtlı bir filo yeni bir gemiye bağlanırsa, bağlanılan gemi mevcut filo kaydını devralır.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;     Üretilecek gemiler için shipyard seçim kriterleri ;&#13;&#10;&#9;* Seçilecek üretim istasyonları için ayarlar menüsünde istediğiniz wharf ya da shipyard için blacklist oluşturabilirsiniz.&#13;&#10;&#9;  1- İlgili istasyon geminin ait olduğu sınıf üretimini yapabiliyor mu?&#13;&#10;&#9;  2- İlgili istasyon gemi şasesini üretebilen istasyon mu?&#13;&#10;&#9;  3- İlgili faction istasyonuna dock edebilecek kadar relation var mı?&#13;&#10;&#9;  4- İlgili istasyonun shiptraderi var mı?&#13;&#10;&#9;  5- Gemiyi üretecek ilgili istasyona ait military ya da capital ship lisansları açık mı?&#13;&#10;&#9;  6- Gemiye takılı ekipmanların (shields, weapons, turrets vb..) blueprintleri ilgili istasyon tarafından karşılanabiliyor mu?&#13;&#10;&#9;  7- İlgili istasyon ve istasyonun bulunduğu sector oyuncu tarafından daha önce keşfedilmiş mi?&#13;&#10;&#9;Bu kriterlerden sonra &#13;&#10;&#9;  Oyuncunun parası yeterli ise (gemi maliyeti seçilen istasyonun sellprice değeri üzerinden hesaplanır) ,&#13;&#10;&#9;  Belirlenen istasyonlar içinde, üretilecek geminin RFM sectörüne en yakın olan ve&#13;&#10;          üretim hattında boş üretim slotu bulunan istasyona öncelik verilir.&#13;&#10;    &#13;&#10;     * Player shipyardlarında her factionun chassis ve equipment blueprintleri öğrenilebildiği için üretim kontrollerinden kolay geçecektir. Böylece daha kolay üretim yapabilirsiniz.&#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;     Gerçek komuta gemisi ölürse Promoted Commander geçici olarak default order görevini yürütür.&#13;&#10;     Gerçek komuta gemisi, inşaatı bittiğinde görevi tekrar devralır.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Not: Filoda hiç gemi yoksa ve üretilemiyorsa yönetim işi için SpecOficer Nurcan ARIKAN HOS ile konuşulabilir. (yazdığım diğer bir mod: upb_equipmentmod_and_recruit_srv )&#13;&#10;&#9;&#13;&#10;Eksiklikler:&#13;&#10;&#9;1- Komutanı istasyon olan RFM'lerde istasyonun yıkılması durumunda istasyon yeniden inşa edilmez.&#13;&#10;&#9;   Bu durumun oluşması durumunda ilgili RFM devre dışı kalacaktır.&#13;&#10;&#9;2- Patlamış gemisi olan bir rfm bir başka rfm ye bağlandığında mevcut gemiler bağlanacak. Patlamış gemi kaydı aktarılmayacak. &#13;&#10;     &#13;&#10;" version="243" date="2024-10-04" save="false" lastupdate="1728074871">
  <!-- upb Lua Loader -->
  <dependency name="upb Lua Loader" id="ws_3265629547" version="100" optional="true" author="netUpb"/>
  <!--Mod support APIs-->
  <dependency name="SirNukes Mod Support APIs" id="ws_2042901274" version="100" optional="true"/>
  <!-- Reaction Force-->
  <dependency name="Reaction Force" id="ws_2463118472" version="207" optional="true" author="Shibdib"/>
  <!-- TaterTrade-->
  <dependency name="TaterTrade" id="ws_2082610969" version="702" optional="true" author="Ludsoe and DeadAir"/>
  <!-- Sector Explorer-->
  <dependency name="Sector Explorer" id="ws_2074838459" version="144" optional="true" author="Assailer"/>
  <!-- Inventory Collector-->
  <dependency name="Inventory Collector" id="ws_2063916598" version="123" optional="true" author="Assailer"/>
  <!-- Sector Patrol-->
  <dependency name="Sector Patrol" id="ws_2458720435" version="111" optional="true" author="Assailer"/>
  <!-- ExtendedConversationMenu on Nexus -->
  <dependency name="Sector Patrol" id="ws_2458720435" version="020" optional="true" author="iforgotmysocks"/>
  <dependency version="300"/>
</content>
